{
  "category": "Vocabulary - Analogies",
  "total_questions": 10,
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Saturday: Sunday",
      "options": [
        "a) wednesday: Friday",
        "b) Sunday: Tuesday",
        "c) Weekend: Weekday",
        "d) Sunday: Monday"
      ],
      "answer": "D"
    },
    {
      "question": "Dog: Puppy",
      "options": [
        "a) Male: Female",
        "b) Cat: Kitten",
        "c) Goat: Bleat",
        "d) Horse: Mare"
      ],
      "answer": "B"
    },
    {
      "question": "Epic: Poem",
      "options": [
        "a) Sonnet: Stanza",
        "b) Lesson: Teach",
        "c) Art: Artist",
        "d) Subject: English"
      ],
      "answer": "D"
    },
    {
      "question": "Cricket: Pitch",
      "options": [
        "a) Crop: Produce",
        "b) Boxer: Ring",
        "c) Run: Bowler",
        "d) Assistant: Officer"
      ],
      "answer": "B"
    },
    {
      "question": "Inch: Centimetre",
      "options": [
        "a) Litre : Height",
        "b) Pound: Weight",
        "c) Kilogram: Heavy",
        "d) Metre: Measurement"
      ],
      "answer": "B"
    },
    {
      "question": "Wool: Knitting",
      "options": [
        "a) Stitching: Cotton",
        "b) Pin: Chair",
        "c) Thread: Crochet",
        "d) Woolen: Winter"
      ],
      "answer": "C"
    },
    {
      "question": "Air: Breathe",
      "options": [
        "a) Rain: Water",
        "b) Time: Watch",
        "c) Wine: Grapes",
        "d) Hen: Cock"
      ],
      "answer": "A"
    },
    {
      "question": "Engineer: Site",
      "options": [
        "a) Man: Woman",
        "b) Medicine: Cure",
        "c) Judge: Justice",
        "d) Doctor: Clinic"
      ],
      "answer": "D"
    },
    {
      "question": "Apple: Orange",
      "options": [
        "a) Banana: Grape",
        "b) Fruit: Health",
        "c) Yellow: Colour",
        "d) Winter: Spring"
      ],
      "answer": "A"
    },
    {
      "question": "District: State",
      "options": [
        "a) Town: Area",
        "b) Capital: Country",
        "c) City: Development",
        "d) Block: Village"
      ],
      "answer": "B"
    }
  ]
}